<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design</title>
    <description>Design Rhyming is project created by Randy Tolentino.
</description>
    <link>http://designrhyming.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://designrhyming.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 20:34:51 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 20:34:51 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Project Infrastructure</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Alright, so in order to get this project going, a lot of placed into laying down a solid foundation. Because this is such a huge and involved undertaking, I feel like I have to be mindful of certain tools, resources, and systems in place. This is critical because there are so many expected outcomes and artifacts that I expect to have by the end of it, and it would foolish to just sloppily overlook the potential value that could be captured along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-am-i-expecting-by-the-end-of-this&quot;&gt;What am I expecting by the end of this?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;One hip hop EP, at least 6 tracks in length&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A website to explain the project&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Research artifacts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Some form of video documentary&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A presentation proposal for SXSW&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;and-how-does-one-accomplish-all-that&quot;&gt;And how does one accomplish all that?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easy&lt;/strong&gt; - the only way all of this can be done is by breaking things down into tiny ass components. There’s no other approach. I’ve dedicated an entire large, hardcover Moleskine journal to write lyrics, pour out ideas, track a calendar, and hold sketches or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-best-part-about-this&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The best part about this&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably the best aspect of this entire endeavour is that this shit is going to be fun! I can’t tell you how excited I am to dedicate so much thought and effort into areas of interest that I am passionate about.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 04:07:15 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://designrhyming.com/2015/11/08/infrastructure.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://designrhyming.com/2015/11/08/infrastructure.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>At Least a Year&#39;s Worth of Work</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the beginning of a large body of work that I’m setting out to accomplish over the next year, maybe longer. Actually, I’m certain it’ll take at least a year and a half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this moment, I’m trying to organize some type of framework in which I will work within. More specifically, gather and note everything that I’ll need, in order to get this project up and running. At the same time, I also have to be mindful of some tools and resources I might need in the months to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHat’s exciting is that this immediately gives me a ton of shit to research, learn, design, build, and share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Updates on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 04:07:15 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://designrhyming.com/2015/11/06/at-least-a-years-worth-of-work.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://designrhyming.com/2015/11/06/at-least-a-years-worth-of-work.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
